

CARRIER OBJECTIVE

To Become A Unique Link In Building A Strong And Rewarding Experience Between Employee & Employer, By Deploying Skills Acquired Through Academic Education and Practical Learnings By Effective & Efficient Management.

I am Passionate for Achievement of Professional and Personnel goals with High Assertiveness and Empathy.

Flexible in Adapting to New Technologies and Acquiring Skillsets.

Positive Attitude combined with Aptitude & Gratitude I want to become a Valuable Asset with No Substitute.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+91 9579603130

WEBSITE:

NITIN SAMIR GOSWAMI

EMAIL:

NITINSAMIRGOSWAMI@GMAIL.COM

AWARDS & RECOGNITION

- Won CFP SIGMA Award In 2023
 For Mangaldeep Agarbatti
- Won GOG (Guardian Of Gold Flake) In 2022 For Driving High Distribution & Sales Number In Gold Flake Category

MR. NITIN SAMIR GOSWAMI

BUSINESS OPERATIONS & MARKETING MANAGER

WORK EXPERIENCE

AREA EXECUTIVE @ ITC LIMITED, JAN 2021 - TILL DATE.

- Leading Loyalty Division for Nagpur Branch, On Shop & In Store Merchandising, Increasing Brand Impact & Strengthening Consumer Base & Inclination Towards Focused Products
- Sales Revenue Of **2.38 Cr** For **Foods** & **0.32 Cr** For **PCP** Division For Nagpur Branch Outlet Base
- Handling 8 Distributors In 8 Cities For Sales & Distribution
 Through A Team Of 46 Salesman & 4 TL's With Sales Revenue
 Of 12 Million ITD
- (Trade Marketing & Distribution) Performing tasks and activities to Establish and Strengthen Trade Relations, Omni Channel Marketing & Vendor Management
- Increasing Distribution Both Volumetric and Weighted Through ATL & BTL Activities
- Conflict resolution, Strategic Planning & Marketing, Capacity Planning, Capital Budget, Claims Settlement, Pay-out Disbursement & Channel Management
- Distribution Management, Facility Management, Inventory Control, Multi Site Operations, Resource Management.
- **(MLCS)** Competitor Analysis and accordingly adapt subsequent Market Level Competitive Strategy.

Sr. ENGINEER @ SHLOKA INFOTECH, APR 2013 - AUG 2019

- Business Process Designing, Requirements Analysis, Delivering Functional Solutions & Blueprint Designing For Businesses
- Configure & Implement SAP Modules To Amplify Functioning, Specifying Interface, Reports, Workflows & Forms
- Business Analysis, Need Identifications, Process Planning & Resource Optimization And Performance Boosting
- Preparation Of Requirement Documents, Wire Frames
 Designs, Process Flow Charts, Dashboards & Business Metrics
- Data Analysis, Extraction, Compilation & Visualization, Log Preparations, Data Warehousing
- Installation Of **ERP**, Systems Servers & Designing IOT systems For Business & Production Requirements
- Analyzing The Critical Avenues & Defects, Customer Service, Needs Assessment For SAP Solution Implementation
- Interactive Presentations, Merchandising, Improving User Interaction & Experience
- Procurement, Managing IT System Development & Implementation, Product Management, Resource Management.
- RFP / RFQ / RFI, Contract Negotiations, Operating Budget,
 Project Deliverables & On Time Completion

COMPETENCIES

- Analytical Data Analysis, Critical Thinking & Logical Reasoning
- Solution Oriented Mindset With Problem Solving Skills
- Strategic Thinking Combining Conceptual Business Situation & Practical Applications
- Strong Presentation Along With Effective Communication & Active Listening Skills
- Strategizing, Planning & Goal Setting
- IN Store Merchandising, Marketing & Branding
- Trade Marketing & Distribution Management
- Cross Functional Team Management

HOBBIES

Learning New Technology.
Cooking & Trying New Recipes
Travelling & Exploring The World

GRADUATE ENGINEER TRAINEE @ SOMA ENTERPRISES, NOV 2012 – MAR 2013.

- **Site In Charge** At **Bridge No.92** Over Vaitarna River at Vaitarna Station Reach 1 For Client **DFCCIL.**
- Site Surveying, Map & Plan Preparation With Hands On Experience On **Total Station** & **Auto Leveler** Equipment
- Quality Control, Requirements Assessments, Reporting & Tracking Project Progress, Risk Assessment & Manpower Management
- Piling, Marine Pile Boring, Girder Casting
- Pile Load & Plate Load Testing.

EDUCATION

MASTERS in BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION [BUSINESS OPERATIONS & MARKETING], SRCOEM 2019-21.

- Secured 7.96 C.G.P.A in First Semester.
- Secured 8.23 C.G.P.A in Second Semester.
- Secured 8.77 C.G.P.A in Third Semester.
- Secured **8.82** C.G.P.A in Fourth Semester.

BACHELORS in ENGINEERING [CIVIL ENGINEERING], SRCOEM, 2012.

Achieved 66.53 % Aggregate.

H.S.S.C [SCIENCE (ELECTRONICS STREAM)], SINDHU MAHAVIDHLAYA, 2007.

• Scored 61 %.

S.S.C HINDUDNYANPEETH CONVENT, 2005.

• Attained 74.40 %.

CERTIFICATIONS

SIX SIGMA GREEN BELT [COURSERA], 24TH SEPTEMBER 2021.

- Six Sigma Advance Define & Measure Phase
- Six Sigma And The Organization (Advance)
- Six Sigma Advance Improve & Control Phase
- Six Sigma Advance Analyze Phase

C & C++ [CHESTER INSTITUTE], 8TH AUGUST 2009.

Coding & Computer Programming Using C Language

MSCIT [M.S.B.T.E], JULY 2006.

• Sustained 94 %.

DECLARATION

I, The Undersigned Hereby Declare That The Information Sto	ated
Above Is True To The Best Of My Knowledge.	

DATE:	(
PLACE:	Mr. NITIN SAMIR GOSWAMI.